Stocks to watch today. Kotto Mahindra
Bank isai Lombard Tata Elky Interarch
Building NLC India 5P AISA Capital in
focus on January 14th.
Stocks to watch January 14th. Stocks
like ISIS, Lombard General Insurance
Company, Tata Elksy, Just Dial,
Interarch Building Solutions, NLC India,
Responsive Industries, Gabian
Technologies India, Victory Electric
Vehicles International and Kodok
Mahindra Bank will be in focus on
January 14th.
Results today. Infosys, HDFC, AMC, ISIS
Credential AMC, Union Bank of India,
Billion Brains Garage Ventures Grow,
Anand Rathish Share and Stock Brokers,
Adidia Burlaw Money, Den Networks, HDB
Financial Services, Indian Overseas
Bank, Mangalore Refinery and
Prochemicals, Network 18 Media and
Investments, Plastabulins India,
Indo-Solar and Wari Renewable Techn
Technologies will announce their
quarterly earnings today. Results on
January 15th.
Geo Financial Services, HDFC Life
Insurance Company, L&T Technology
Services, 361WAM,
Aloque Industries, Angel 1, DB Corp.
Delta Corp. MV Photovoltaic Power, Fed
Bank Financial Services, Mang Alam Drugs
and Organics, Nelco, Novako Vistas
Corporation, Smart Works Cow or King
Spaces, South Indian Bank, Swarage
Engines and Sterling and Wilson
Renewable Energy will release their
quarterly earnings on January 15th.
Stocks to watch. Interarch Building
Solutions.
The company has received an order worth
Rs 130 crore for the manufacturing of a
pre-engineered steel building system NLC
India. The company has signed a
memorandum of understanding Mao with the
Gujarat government for the development
of large-scale renewable energy projects
in the state. These include solar, wind,
hybrid and battery energy storage
projects with an investment potential of
Rs 25,000 cr. Carneaka bank. The bank
has enabled a facility for the payment
of Carneaka government SK2e receipts
through its internet banking platform
providing a secure realtime and
paperless receipt system. Thomas Cook
India. The company has signed a
memorandum of understanding Mao with the
Gujarat government to boost and promote
Gujarat s domestic tourism
responsive industries.
Bavit Singh Chhatta has resigned as the
chief financial officer CFO of the
company effective January 12th due to
personal reasons.
The company is in the process of
appointing a suitable candidate for the
position of CFO and key managerial
personnel KMP.
Bulk deals. Gabian Technologies India
Alternative Investment Fund Vorton
Opportunities Fund was the largest buyer
acquiring an additional 4.97 lock shares
equivalent to 3.66% of the paid up
equity at Rs 89 per share amounting to
Rs 4.42 42 crore. Vorton already held a
1.01%
stake 1.37 lock shares in Gabian
Technologies.
Further, Royal Alpha growthbacked Royal
Alpha Opportunity Fund acquired 99,200
equity shares in Gabian at Rs 89 per
share for Rs 88.28 lock. Kimal Kumar
Duger and CO also bought the same number
of shares at Rs 84.55
per share for Rs 83.87 lock.
Additionally, Nexus Equity Growth Fund
Scheme 1 picked up 1.48 lock shares in
Gabian at Rs 84.55
per share for Rs 1.25 25 crme
listing Victory Electric Vehicles
International
Yajour fibers
stocks trade X date for a split Kotto
Mahindra Bank Ammer realy and infradia
stocks in FN ON
Samine Capital
sale disclaimer this article provides
stock market news forformational
purposes only and should not be
construed as investment advice.
Readers are encouraged to consult with a
qualified financial adviser before
making any investment decisions.